Hola a todos, femininos, to Tiny Desk.
It's hard to put into words how much
the huge honor is to be here.
And this amazing place and play with this wonderful musician,
started with Master Gonzalo Rubelcava on the piano.
And we have Kush Abadi on the drums
and Pavlominares on the bass.
And even more special is to be able to present this beautiful
music from my latest, Blue Nut Release, which is called Feeling.
I'm feeling is a musical movement that happened in Cuba during the 40s and 60s, where musicians
were very inspired by jazz, amboletos, and South American literature.
And most of the music from our latest album is from that time period.
The first thing that we play is one called Dimasi de Sto, tell me if it's you.
It's one of tune from one of the most prominent figures from that time.
His name is José Antonio Mendez.
And we're going to continue with another beautiful song by Frank Dominguez.
This is called Imaginus Images.
And it's a love song that talks about somebody that meets their true love.
but they leave them way too fast.
And this song is about the memories that the person lives behind
and the empty feelings, empty spaces that are created from that
moment. This is also an arrangement by Gonzalo
and this is called Immaculance.
And thank you. So the last two songs that we're going to play,
this one is called Leader Church, it's a song that was made,
was written by her metal pasquelle, who has transitioned not too long ago.
And it was made famous by a famous myelave's album, Life Evil.
And this is also an arrangement by Gonzalo.
And after that, we're going to finish with a renal of mine from my previous
Blue Note release, which is called Echoes of the Inner Prophet.
And the name of the song is unconscious whisper.